{"question":"106028 - 27722 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83711 - 9737 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73974", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53846 + 18637 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80001 - 284 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83621 - 9495 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74126", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60354 + 29394 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89748", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100807 - 6100 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86384 - 14125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72259", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80124 + 3954 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84078", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120107 - 25744 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94363", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111277 - 9084 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102193", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69046 + 31125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100171", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104075 - 21104 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82971", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123325 - 25569 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97756", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90867 + 7905 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102082 - 11803 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115951 - 22196 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57551 + 26583 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110400 - 18451 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91949", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97821 - 12389 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85432", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92194 + 9294 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101488", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100020 - 29027 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70993", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92658 - 9961 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82697", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65557 + 12292 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77849", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107601 - 13809 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115394 - 27888 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87506", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73040 + 27071 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101703 - 21499 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80204", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98783 - 15459 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83324", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92234 + 2316 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94550", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107508 - 20131 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94272 - 6583 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78212 + 13929 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92141", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107086 - 12651 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111154 - 24885 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86269", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56498 + 18959 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105036 - 31748 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121137 - 27815 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93322", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47914 + 31691 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79605", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102072 - 8799 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112135 - 31350 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80785", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85606 + 2552 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88158", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101045 - 29006 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72039", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123438 - 20750 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83686 + 10919 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94605", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102001 - 16689 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83354 - 9706 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73648", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71097 + 24400 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95497", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100306 - 18501 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117438 - 19281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71747 + 15126 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86873", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101201 - 31088 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70113", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99485 - 24015 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91894 + 9623 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101517", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104304 - 15830 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88474", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78394 - 7115 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82469 + 13970 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96439", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108038 - 15385 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113146 - 26573 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86573", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57289 + 18970 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76259", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103079 - 31960 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132382 - 30183 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102199", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60721 + 16771 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77492", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108048 - 9836 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98212", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85854 - 7776 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78078", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93433 + 3461 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96894", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110502 - 28736 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81766", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97273 - 9443 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87830", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57290 + 14791 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72081", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102002 - 9237 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92765", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113148 - 25644 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87504", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66390 + 32703 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99093", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107904 - 8801 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99103", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92781 - 12695 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80086", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82989 + 19628 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102617", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120006 - 31495 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88511", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126172 - 24934 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101238", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56439 + 26813 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83252", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100305 - 28953 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113684 - 11557 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102127", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60545 + 13644 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74189", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102103 - 23225 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78878", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97761 - 23869 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73892", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53499 + 20990 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120005 - 26529 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87178 - 13276 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63603 + 14355 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77958", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100071 - 15929 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84142", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95461 - 15464 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79997", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64307 + 10677 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74984", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106704 - 5109 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101595", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91452 - 3150 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88302", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93013 + 1300 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94313", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105508 - 14363 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128936 - 31721 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97215", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64595 + 21456 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86051", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105701 - 28281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81754 - 351 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49346 + 26828 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76174", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109085 - 30395 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87269 - 15203 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72066", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70817 + 12185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110604 - 29193 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81411", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117274 - 24882 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92392", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42018 + 31939 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73957", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106803 - 23921 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82882", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113295 - 27636 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85659", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73890 + 16840 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104052 - 16703 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87349", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131648 - 30686 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100962", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68273 + 28872 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107080 - 10186 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96894", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87652 - 12423 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84818 + 1575 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86393", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104044 - 1533 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102511", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97576 - 954 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96622", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74700 + 16955 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91655", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101009 - 1450 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99559", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98465 - 20274 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78191", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84848 + 9480 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94328", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104504 - 26842 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77662", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113317 - 27631 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85686", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74589 + 5351 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79940", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105016 - 7500 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97516", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91494 - 14716 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73977 + 17139 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103404 - 32510 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70894", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92463 - 15636 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76827", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74991 + 16350 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91341", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80705 - 7253 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73452", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87324 - 8656 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58623 + 18938 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77561", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101402 - 3496 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97906", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112828 - 12995 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99833", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81594 + 17778 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99372", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105038 - 9768 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99281 - 1795 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97486", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99133 + 3010 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102143", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90107 - 11418 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95870 - 3946 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54848 + 22026 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76874", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100705 - 3119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97586", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91473 - 18016 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87909 + 2905 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90814", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110605 - 30208 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80397", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96513 - 6965 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67806 + 26118 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107050 - 9435 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97615", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112835 - 32144 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80691", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76344 + 4170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80514", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103085 - 9599 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93486", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128936 - 27281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101655", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57122 + 31532 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105078 - 7800 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97278", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116850 - 31129 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85721", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73980 + 17438 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91418", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104506 - 32654 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112285 - 11995 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100290", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68082 + 9435 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77517", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106092 - 24771 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81321", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77298 - 771 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72534 + 10428 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82962", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100067 - 26956 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94141 - 2453 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64926 + 9546 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109108 - 25506 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114825 - 31592 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83233", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57523 + 20543 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78066", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107081 - 10819 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75460 - 3896 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77652 + 8924 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130406 - 28514 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101892", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93898 - 10261 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83637", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75523 + 4303 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79826", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103109 - 20992 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82117", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115834 - 27062 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88777 + 4614 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100069 - 1822 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78932 - 4224 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74708", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69708 + 25277 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94985", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106405 - 13752 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114553 - 27316 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87237", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83275 + 15119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98394", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103016 - 8837 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94179", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114220 - 20032 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94188", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42688 + 28095 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70783", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102900 - 27601 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75299", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116297 - 29326 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86971", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70816 + 23717 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94533", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90609 - 16671 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73938", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91997 - 9842 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61970 + 9748 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71718", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108077 - 19396 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88681", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96337 - 1771 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94566", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71043 + 4846 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75889", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105204 - 28983 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76221", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114720 - 15754 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98966", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72261 + 22442 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94703", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105700 - 3669 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102031", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84661 - 4341 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99833 + 1162 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107601 - 18698 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88903", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99595 - 12736 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85895 + 6438 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92333", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110803 - 9682 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101121", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93697 - 9702 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82167 + 983 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102005 - 31370 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70635", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122532 - 31762 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90770", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95102 + 2791 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97893", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104068 - 23155 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80913", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124251 - 21890 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102361", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88875 + 10380 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99255", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109307 - 11637 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98183 - 1061 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43164 + 27279 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107407 - 28950 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86427 - 176 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86251", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59423 + 26303 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85726", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109606 - 25361 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84245", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114574 - 25930 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88644", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75456 + 4597 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102409 - 31660 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111588 - 13817 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57389 + 30925 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88314", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107013 - 11515 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95498", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118650 - 27246 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91404", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73863 + 17481 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91344", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110500 - 13762 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96738", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92342 - 17542 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71955 + 2070 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74025", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100202 - 10570 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89632", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118652 - 24699 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93953", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96805 + 4862 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101065 - 14000 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76593 - 1530 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75063", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91430 + 3057 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94487", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107609 - 7359 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117117 - 29831 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87286", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82234 + 8206 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104003 - 26968 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77035", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119143 - 26325 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65218 + 19149 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84367", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105101 - 29563 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75538", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116421 - 16890 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99531", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73060 + 29320 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103049 - 10608 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92441", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123713 - 23126 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100587", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59194 + 19975 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79169", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100010 - 14295 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85715", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89893 - 9075 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69821 + 9448 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79269", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104028 - 27673 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78230 - 8039 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70191", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80589 + 20901 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101490", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105201 - 29878 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75323", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87799 - 7783 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80016", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47793 + 26885 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74678", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80305 - 9470 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70835", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94283 - 9185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85098", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50994 + 19181 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70175", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105061 - 30031 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75030", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119584 - 27121 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92463", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79968 + 16090 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96058", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104706 - 2684 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102022", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92768 - 2675 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90093", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56777 + 26565 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83342", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108805 - 32460 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76345", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123767 - 23817 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99950", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90767 + 6395 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100095 - 16339 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83756", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81335 - 6025 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75310", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76541 + 9525 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86066", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109086 - 11762 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97324", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91291 - 21108 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80385 + 2699 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83084", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108065 - 25282 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82783", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85950 - 10897 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69588 + 28914 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98502", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103049 - 13196 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89853", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122855 - 32075 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52288 + 21409 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73697", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110100 - 16295 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81213 - 2646 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78567", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75171 + 2882 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107043 - 17521 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115379 - 16229 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74686 + 25738 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100424", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106033 - 11656 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113667 - 15335 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98332", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80611 + 19448 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100059", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101802 - 28302 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115610 - 29863 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85747", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62694 + 11452 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74146", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104403 - 30670 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73733", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98571 - 19189 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70642 + 4213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74855", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101017 - 28931 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72086", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84429 - 5979 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93705 + 7591 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101296", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101037 - 12540 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88497", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113761 - 21349 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88225 + 4 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102302 - 16985 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117366 - 26212 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72489 + 1081 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101093 - 30117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99937 - 12343 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87594", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74351 + 17361 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91712", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100097 - 24241 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98791 - 28445 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70346", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82872 + 17363 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106064 - 6708 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99356", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76224 - 1960 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85261 + 10473 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95734", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103013 - 31013 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88559 - 7656 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80903", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47588 + 26581 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74169", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105023 - 21316 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73798 - 1586 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72212", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62078 + 29300 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91378", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101041 - 13907 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111411 - 23054 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76616 + 7261 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83877", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105008 - 15889 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93845 - 9860 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83985", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80758 + 8757 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89515", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90003 - 8284 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81719", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99519 - 24964 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73451 + 17466 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90917", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107404 - 17569 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89835", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95327 - 19814 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62963 + 8392 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106404 - 24607 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81797", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111129 - 28605 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82524", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69890 + 5978 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75868", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102040 - 18280 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83760", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91444 - 5280 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86164", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91476 + 7698 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99174", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103068 - 19291 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95457 - 21959 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73498", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80736 + 5663 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86399", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104074 - 4070 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100004", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122398 - 23770 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98628", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66292 + 28450 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102102 - 5061 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97041", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134699 - 32395 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42918 + 29969 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72887", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104022 - 31080 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72942", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95254 - 23629 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70402 + 20049 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101021 - 13317 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87704", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112426 - 15529 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96897", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65638 + 10213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103085 - 25355 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99195 - 21213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77982", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91041 + 3305 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94346", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106606 - 21604 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75721 - 373 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67559 + 5837 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73396", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103100 - 19682 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83418", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77628 - 3996 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73632", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99611 + 2036 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104016 - 32389 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81862 - 960 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60561 + 18299 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106209 - 15079 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91130", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93383 - 6605 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88994 + 7229 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107094 - 32323 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122190 - 24824 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60408 + 17886 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78294", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105402 - 28140 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111967 - 26723 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85244", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70553 + 23788 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94341", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101050 - 30132 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114232 - 23041 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91191", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55386 + 32369 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106076 - 8186 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86594 - 9896 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76698", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60314 + 29529 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120308 - 28323 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91985", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92436 - 10958 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81478", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72312 + 18448 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90760", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102100 - 9762 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92338", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117714 - 22802 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94912", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82681 + 7330 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90011", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104098 - 31164 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72934", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131850 - 29586 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78418 + 20537 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98955", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105107 - 32042 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121747 - 23425 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98322", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70943 + 22565 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108026 - 28925 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124744 - 23926 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81190 + 7600 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88790", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90801 - 20418 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70383", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"133421 - 32021 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70232 + 3923 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108057 - 20118 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87939", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96319 - 13226 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83093", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76798 + 20831 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97629", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102107 - 13356 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88751", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99123 - 27699 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71424", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84165 + 1032 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85197", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101301 - 22177 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79124", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112642 - 9971 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102671", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72336 + 4950 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77286", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105608 - 16680 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88928", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79196 - 5471 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90736 + 2971 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108801 - 31141 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77660", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99717 - 2936 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96781", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60177 + 26330 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86507", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107300 - 12863 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131725 - 29824 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64041 + 6345 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80300 - 7727 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72573", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96496 - 17645 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47869 + 31715 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108099 - 11987 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96112", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79942 - 1301 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78641", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68438 + 27221 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95659", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90603 - 6455 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84148", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95265 - 9846 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85419", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65553 + 30835 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100035 - 6207 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112891 - 17888 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95003", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78238 + 20353 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98591", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106107 - 27727 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113453 - 20678 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92775", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50239 + 25885 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76124", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109098 - 17277 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91821", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"133127 - 32473 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72708 + 22674 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105609 - 4077 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101532", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98162 - 25892 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60205 + 30656 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90861", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106033 - 18290 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87743", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76619 - 5369 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63856 + 25676 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89532", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100007 - 5664 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115490 - 15097 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100393", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51744 + 25319 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77063", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101051 - 25007 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76044", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114430 - 18484 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95946", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78512 + 6835 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85347", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109070 - 13807 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95263", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95662 - 18700 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76962", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55004 + 24228 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103070 - 26954 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75312 - 1540 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67162 + 23393 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104039 - 30876 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73163", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114523 - 29926 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84597", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58680 + 22608 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105308 - 29662 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99797 - 22608 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77189", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65756 + 21885 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87641", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105404 - 16430 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88974", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113927 - 19122 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84271 + 8356 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109706 - 10667 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99039", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89952 - 4928 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85024", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54577 + 17208 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71785", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106014 - 18537 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87477", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121979 - 32692 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68469 + 30954 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99423", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101909 - 8723 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93186", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74729 - 207 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83256 + 4287 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87543", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101036 - 13946 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87090", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94984 - 7165 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87819", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59022 + 27665 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86687", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101024 - 28511 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129117 - 28918 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100199", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98122 + 666 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98788", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105600 - 24679 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80921", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84322 - 11600 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72722", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84454 + 12822 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107501 - 7030 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100471", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124266 - 31651 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92615", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61230 + 20681 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102208 - 31899 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70309", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88288 - 635 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100434 + 1505 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101939", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108042 - 12908 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98980 - 7573 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91407", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56280 + 27928 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101304 - 30261 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71043", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117814 - 32110 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85704", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67694 + 8027 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75721", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106704 - 10336 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96368", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97737 - 5368 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92369", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82660 + 7863 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90523", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101507 - 2455 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91365 - 15059 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59676 + 17067 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76743", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105062 - 9890 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95172", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96732 - 11600 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85132", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58350 + 23156 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81506", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104100 - 10026 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94074", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113692 - 14833 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81968 + 1438 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80306 - 1963 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98988 - 16277 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82711", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69174 + 27796 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80200 - 6302 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123846 - 23833 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100013", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69521 + 605 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70126", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101901 - 10180 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91721", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94451 - 16599 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91688 + 464 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104081 - 6304 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86831 - 7844 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78987", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71204 + 25406 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100705 - 19035 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96128 - 21296 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74832", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78393 + 14483 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92876", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106402 - 27547 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78855", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75943 - 180 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75763", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61847 + 15958 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107039 - 12183 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127117 - 30846 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67605 + 21131 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88736", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90709 - 3230 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87479", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99773 - 13085 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74645 + 11497 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86142", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130504 - 32021 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111548 - 27286 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54527 + 30549 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85076", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108403 - 20533 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89857 - 10179 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79678", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84719 + 10728 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95447", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101702 - 8219 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87544 - 5620 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65436 + 15236 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108091 - 16297 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91794", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89922 - 10247 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79675", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98598 + 3208 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101806", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105505 - 15043 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90462", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114692 - 16453 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98239", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68687 + 12045 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80732", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106086 - 17715 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88371", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93953 - 14810 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79143", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75885 + 16423 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92308", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108608 - 18458 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97378 - 7256 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92605 + 650 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93255", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101407 - 20213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81194", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93193 - 5452 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87741", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69869 + 13256 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83125", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108906 - 8088 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97226 - 25427 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71799", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73889 + 2797 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76686", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102057 - 27214 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122462 - 21815 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76624 + 23715 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100339", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109202 - 8420 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100782", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123971 - 26810 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97161", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99029 + 2009 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101038", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108203 - 12977 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95226", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83273 - 9619 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59086 + 14291 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90302 - 7826 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81274 - 7110 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74164", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91663 + 3989 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100080 - 27034 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73046", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118190 - 31233 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86957", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61730 + 31905 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93635", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103031 - 10661 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92370", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97618 - 8175 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81909 + 3858 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85767", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102047 - 24106 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77941", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116611 - 16117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100494", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66329 + 6584 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72913", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105023 - 7475 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91377 - 7744 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83633", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73469 + 1824 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107401 - 29333 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119219 - 30331 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88888", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64016 + 17443 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105090 - 12621 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92469", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87630 - 1125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86505", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82260 + 8324 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103609 - 16653 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86956", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129381 - 27341 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72318 + 29983 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105807 - 25318 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89878 - 2119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87759", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78724 + 9894 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106009 - 7213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98796", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84668 - 14200 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70468", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79757 + 922 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80679", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106085 - 30354 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75731", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88993 - 3223 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85770", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68619 + 30598 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99217", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105066 - 15096 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99158 - 16961 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82197", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74243 + 28369 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80205 - 1348 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78857", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111441 - 22049 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89392", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54201 + 18160 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72361", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110402 - 30507 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79895", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91980 - 17053 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74927", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60384 + 16772 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77156", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108408 - 26169 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82239", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123527 - 32024 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91503", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90822 + 281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91103", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107004 - 4893 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114170 - 20197 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93973", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82266 + 19733 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101999", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105907 - 5089 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112636 - 16770 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95866", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65115 + 31549 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96664", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108084 - 5616 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102468", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118945 - 21632 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97313", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76178 + 24743 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100921", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108078 - 23497 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87251 - 6145 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81106", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73133 + 7309 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80442", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104057 - 28884 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75173", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124794 - 27596 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97198", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77341 + 8047 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109200 - 24434 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84766", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98595 - 8848 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89747", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66169 + 30161 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96330", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108005 - 24606 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83399", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89489 - 14887 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64616 + 10086 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106059 - 8697 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97362", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115954 - 23119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92835", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67668 + 7529 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75197", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108047 - 5472 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102575", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113978 - 18553 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58926 + 30523 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104501 - 4678 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99823", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127756 - 27624 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100132", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77555 + 2340 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79895", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101407 - 31394 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70013", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84110 - 5063 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70661 + 25658 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96319", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101502 - 15731 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86181 - 1333 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84848", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83012 + 611 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107031 - 17009 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90022", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126297 - 29539 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50407 + 21921 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72328", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106106 - 12631 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93475", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86595 - 14433 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75714 + 4511 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106034 - 6449 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99585", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84229 - 13107 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60302 + 19721 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80023", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105073 - 6070 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99003", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97644 - 21183 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76461", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67769 + 25528 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93297", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108102 - 10944 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97158", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81491 - 6984 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74507", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70080 + 5921 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76001", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105301 - 20232 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85069", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122832 - 28917 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93915", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92372 + 8401 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100773", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104010 - 20922 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83088", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113351 - 30793 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82558", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53321 + 17774 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71095", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90208 - 9032 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91788 - 6986 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84802", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70303 + 23476 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93779", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107905 - 23214 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84691", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94946 - 3351 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91595", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64930 + 23513 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102038 - 12641 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89397", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119765 - 20412 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99353", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64346 + 12441 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76787", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109094 - 12042 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114988 - 30123 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84865", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53167 + 22332 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75499", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108021 - 31683 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76338", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117449 - 15619 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101830", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58005 + 17436 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75441", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104308 - 2203 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98934 - 24620 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74314", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80880 + 10494 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91374", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100086 - 25003 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75083", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86283 - 11334 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74949", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48863 + 27514 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105906 - 25260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96148 - 2628 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68287 + 32702 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100989", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105062 - 7615 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97447", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79677 - 3988 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59077 + 22834 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101001 - 28042 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72959", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126255 - 24134 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102121", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65936 + 21201 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87137", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104024 - 19319 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84705", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99224 - 1980 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97244", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84076 + 12035 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101308 - 22697 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128669 - 26998 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101671", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91192 + 7281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98473", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103302 - 11683 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91619", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99542 - 25834 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73708", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75545 + 20093 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95638", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104090 - 3740 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98326 - 12031 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86295", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66031 + 12636 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108004 - 26090 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81914", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85564 - 12827 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72737", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58812 + 17053 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75865", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102027 - 7726 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85881 - 3698 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64397 + 10459 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100044 - 24965 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75079", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99315 - 5283 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53955 + 19025 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72980", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104201 - 31615 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72586", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96187 - 3750 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88362 + 6720 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95082", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103504 - 18918 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84586", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87444 - 8111 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79333", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77089 + 23403 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100492", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100805 - 8542 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92263", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115246 - 19865 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95381", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78530 + 21610 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100140", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105605 - 24624 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80981", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83267 - 6670 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76597", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65980 + 32596 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107406 - 23003 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97364 - 17538 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79826", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89301 + 6086 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95387", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105074 - 6087 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98987", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71393 - 402 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70991", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71961 + 262 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105088 - 26324 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78764", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116493 - 16934 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99559", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72135 + 14167 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86302", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109024 - 9486 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99538", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91581 - 13150 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78431", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92498 + 952 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101066 - 27794 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73272", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125113 - 26937 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68449 + 32067 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100516", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70503 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83925 - 4426 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79499", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85882 + 15020 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102088 - 31205 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70883", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88633 - 5977 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71121 + 1650 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103099 - 16567 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86532", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97560 - 5093 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92467", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83530 + 6340 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109057 - 32099 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76958", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87461 - 5431 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82030", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53883 + 25438 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79321", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100025 - 2698 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97327", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95559 - 8076 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78043 + 734 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104050 - 9360 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91767 - 8765 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95262 + 4900 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80908 - 9299 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71609", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89539 - 19298 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70241", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45527 + 31648 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77175", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109065 - 30717 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99853 - 10254 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89599", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71344 + 25679 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97023", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106048 - 26852 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79196", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92331 - 1618 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98244 + 3909 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102153", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100404 - 263 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100141", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92250 - 6211 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86039", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61301 + 24093 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85394", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102303 - 32103 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91165 - 16763 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50809 + 32589 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83398", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90604 - 4153 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96648 - 3218 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65996 + 10870 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76866", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109702 - 26247 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83455", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116873 - 29667 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71572 + 26802 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98374", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103080 - 6392 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82691 - 9117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73574", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86634 + 2752 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105403 - 9533 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123458 - 21306 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72148 + 4102 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100409 - 25951 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74458", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99517 - 7972 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91545", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86598 + 9581 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96179", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100062 - 1313 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119962 - 24000 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95962", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77814 + 24574 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103705 - 13661 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90044", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117522 - 32037 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57925 + 14870 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108900 - 18195 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90705", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119947 - 23671 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92590 + 8170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100760", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102103 - 19321 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82782", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119489 - 19170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100319", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60416 + 15675 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76091", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102607 - 31722 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70885", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82141 - 1835 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80841 + 18358 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99199", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100802 - 10191 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87174 - 1106 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84677 + 16015 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100692", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107019 - 10958 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96061", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129971 - 27786 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102185", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53859 + 25260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108200 - 26077 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82123", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116811 - 19708 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97103", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47125 + 26162 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102065 - 3622 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77472 - 879 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76593", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65619 + 28931 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94550", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107095 - 13054 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94041", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86882 - 16078 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70804", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74112 + 24388 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105409 - 18716 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86693", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111139 - 13127 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98012", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75035 + 22723 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109040 - 6361 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102679", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119517 - 22641 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96876", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89037 + 9719 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98756", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105700 - 6240 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99460", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89481 - 8127 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81354", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73053 + 12290 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105021 - 19455 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85566", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96392 - 23169 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78763 + 23825 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90909 - 20702 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70207", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111731 - 13812 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97919", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69095 + 2333 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71428", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109039 - 12130 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96909", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87633 - 5997 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81636", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93329 + 1881 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95210", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105075 - 17974 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116640 - 17214 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99426", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86359 + 4 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86363", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80007 - 9650 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97169 - 21487 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57280 + 17652 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74932", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108604 - 32121 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96718 - 19869 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76849", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59429 + 11816 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71245", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100061 - 18604 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98919 - 1148 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73946 + 9198 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83144", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103050 - 16044 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87006", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79995 - 903 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88600 + 9806 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103903 - 10430 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93473", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115442 - 21574 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93868", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87398 + 10644 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98042", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105091 - 9867 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84882 - 2748 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85177 + 15050 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100227", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106053 - 25279 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119375 - 29849 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89526", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70930 + 31341 = ?","answers":[{"value":"102271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105904 - 8606 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97298", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97326 - 389 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96937", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86009 + 2809 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105051 - 11622 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93429", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92712 - 9346 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69701 + 11841 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81542", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106073 - 21646 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84427", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87262 - 337 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86925", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94392 + 4442 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98834", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104065 - 30680 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73385", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72116 - 1504 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83706 + 13794 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101020 - 5706 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95314", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116784 - 27011 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89773", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75869 + 620 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110901 - 30828 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80073", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123820 - 26478 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97342", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67270 + 31673 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98943", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110906 - 17056 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93850", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117383 - 20600 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96783", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81283 + 10540 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91823", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90707 - 13024 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119120 - 29256 = ?","answers":[{"value":"89864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86276 + 7088 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105038 - 5975 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99063", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95384 - 10036 = ?","answers":[{"value":"85348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66420 + 26853 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103000 - 5032 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97968", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115931 - 16898 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99033", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75254 + 4532 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79786", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109004 - 25465 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83539", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115813 - 31913 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52916 + 27254 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100602 - 19363 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81239", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91324 - 13835 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77783 + 22072 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99855", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108068 - 19335 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88733", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112156 - 18443 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83316 + 4978 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88294", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103010 - 23530 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79480", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111659 - 27464 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84195", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54142 + 22368 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107074 - 7369 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99705", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97799 - 1241 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96558", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65520 + 21525 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87045", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100060 - 16391 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83669", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96331 - 284 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63518 + 24434 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87952", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110805 - 28549 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125538 - 26042 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63428 + 7276 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70704", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102001 - 702 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101299", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87264 - 10040 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76505 + 19884 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96389", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109091 - 24532 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84559", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81962 - 3730 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69810 + 24698 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110901 - 27671 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83230", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87565 - 15213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73174 + 308 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109203 - 9003 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111817 - 17974 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86379 + 13728 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100107", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104010 - 5090 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98920", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89791 - 953 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88838", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77420 + 8947 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86367", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103408 - 2912 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122239 - 24187 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59841 + 12227 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105508 - 14213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91295", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127273 - 29935 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97338", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70962 + 24199 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95161", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106808 - 11561 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87939 - 7144 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71860 + 882 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100089 - 27260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72829", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88260 - 17096 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71164", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69364 + 6159 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75523", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107088 - 18912 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91721 - 8907 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82814", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75748 + 4964 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80712", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106025 - 31411 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74614", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79816 - 5664 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74769 + 1055 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75824", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110202 - 25321 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84881", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115538 - 14027 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101511", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83908 + 17787 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101695", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120109 - 21529 = ?","answers":[{"value":"98580", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88857 - 9241 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79616", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61040 + 16636 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77676", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105803 - 5064 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100739", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85257 - 14090 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71167", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69207 + 22122 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91329", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103040 - 30703 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72337", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116840 - 29598 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59977 + 18133 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78110", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109093 - 21918 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87175", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111166 - 31558 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64636 + 13335 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77971", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102605 - 7225 = ?","answers":[{"value":"95380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86426 - 2969 = ?","answers":[{"value":"83457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65149 + 8047 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73196", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102076 - 27270 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74806", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73662 - 356 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68954 + 22119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91073", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103201 - 18296 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84905", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73390 - 2384 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71006", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57818 + 19954 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106049 - 6131 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79826 - 2158 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80305 + 7391 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87696", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106702 - 19842 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124499 - 32227 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92272", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85496 + 15304 = ?","answers":[{"value":"100800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109700 - 16224 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96210 - 21889 = ?","answers":[{"value":"74321", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86662 + 4888 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91550", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102507 - 4880 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119462 - 17902 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81378 + 12627 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94005", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110700 - 23494 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117860 - 25654 = ?","answers":[{"value":"92206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58447 + 19416 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103080 - 14967 = ?","answers":[{"value":"88113", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99993 - 27238 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66514 + 29909 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96423", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110300 - 27346 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82954", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98782 - 8762 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90020", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80578 + 12777 = ?","answers":[{"value":"93355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100035 - 8479 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93826 - 22119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66874 + 32167 = ?","answers":[{"value":"99041", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102702 - 12442 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90260", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99527 - 9070 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74632 + 9707 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84339", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
